你会在示例代码中看见，
You'll also notice in the sample code that we
我们在其中调用了log.e，这是用来记录错误消息的。
have lines that call log.e, which log error messages. With
我们可以将插入的设备，放到命令行中使用adb命令进行调试
the adb command line tool and with the device plugged
当你键入adb logcat命令时，
in, you can type adb logcat to see the debug
你可以看见调试信息和错误信息正在被打印出来。
and error messages that are being printed to the logcat.
更多关于logcat命令的使用，你可以参考下面的链接。
For more details on the logcat options, see the link
另一种调试的方法，是使用Android Studio查看日志。
below. Another way to view the logs, is to use
当你点击屏幕上的这个按钮时，
Android Studio. If you click on the Screen Android button,
它启动了Android设备监视器。
it launches the Android Device Monitor. Which includes the
这当中还有了DDMS工具，关于这个Rado有在之前的课程中提过。
DDMS tool that Rado mentioned earlier. Then click on a
然后点击这个有我们的应用程序的设备，你可以看见这是一个正在运行的程序。
device and you can see that our app here, is
如果您在此处点击LogCat这个选项卡，
a running process. If you click on the LogCat tab,
那么你会看到所有的日志消息，
then you all these log messages here, which is what
这就是我们看到的adb logcat。
we saw with adb logcat. Now try viewing the logs
现在，使用其中任意一个方法，查看自己程序的日志。
yourself with either of those methods. If you do both,
如果你都做到了，那么将对你刮目相看。 选中此框，继续。
then you get brownie points. Check this box to proceed.